themeworld.com 2004-06-05

# Danworld Network: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Danworld, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all our websites. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our sites. 

This site contains links to other sites. **Danworld, Inc.** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Third-Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

**Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. We use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. 

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
This site gives users the following options for correcting and/or removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

    **Dan Piparo**
    **Danworld, Inc.**
    **3621 Horatio Street**
    **Tampa, FL 33609**
    **(888) 4-DANWORLD**
    **Contact Us**
